pcregistryshield.com 2017-12-05

# Privacy Policy - ShieldApps

## Shieldapps Software (Shieldapps Software Innovations, Shieldapps) Privacy Policy

SHIELDAPPS IS COMMITTED TO PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU MAY PROVIDE TO US WHEN USING ANY OF OUR ONLINE SERVICES AND ONLINE/OFFLINE SOFTWARE. THIS PRIVACY POLICY DESCRIBES HOW WE TREAT INFORMATION WE ARE EXPOSED TO WHEN YOU ARE USING OUR SOFTWARE.

**Information Collection**

When you install or purchase or download trial or evaluation versions, or register a ShieldApps software, we may collect personal information including your name, address, email address, etc. for the purpose of recording the transaction when you engage in activities on our web site or within the ShieldApps software. When we use a payment-processing merchant we ensure that the same strict privacy criteria are in place. We do not (knowingly) collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen. We also give users the option of receiving useful product information (such as updates, alerts and associated product offerings), via permission based emailing platform. We fully ensure your privacy and value your trust. We will never sell, rent, lease or trade your personal information to any third party. Likewise, your information will not be shared with a third party in any other way unless ShieldApps is required to do so by law. ShieldApps may engage the services of a third party from time to time and may provide certain information that includes personal information in order for the third party to perform such services. Any third parties who provide services to ShieldApps have agreed not to disclose your information or use it for any other purpose, and are required to implement or adopt a Privacy Policy that is no less stringent than ShieldApps’ Privacy Policy. You may opt out of receiving emails from us at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email.

By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to ShieldApps collection, use, and disclosure of such information for the purposes as outlined herein. Any information that you post to a chat room, public bulletin, social networks or forum is available to all permitted users of that site. ShieldApps cannot control, nor is it responsible for the use, disclosure, or dissemination of such information by any third parties.

**Web Site Usage**

We may automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information when you access our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors navigate our sites on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors, length of visits, etc.

**Software Usage**

We automatically collect standard usage information when you install our software (such as but not limited to your operating system installation language, installed software, browser records, stored 3rd and other information that is needed for our software to fulfill its purpose). This information helps us provide you with our technical services as they are described in the software that you have installed.

**How Information Is Used When Collected**

We may use information collected in the following ways:

• To process, validate and verify purchases.

• To contact you to reconfirm or verify accuracy of information provided.

• To register you as a customer.

• To open and maintain a support account for you.

• To send email notifications about new, existing, enhanced products or services.

• To send information on special offers, or to obtain your feedback to help enhance existing features or provide added products and services.

• To enable us to personalize content, advertising and promotions based on preferences, needs, suggestions, or recommendations.

• To provide advance notice of termination of a trial period or an opportunity to extend a trial period, or advance notice of expiration of your software license.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example protect our intellectual property rights), and your compliance with the applicable End User License Agreement(s) contained within the ShieldApps software. We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the applicable law may require us to do so.

**Cookies**

We define a cookie as any string of data and information that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our services. ShieldApps utilizes cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our services. This information enables us to deliver faster service capabilities to our customers or to our affiliates and/or other sales partners, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All ShieldApps cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to ShieldApps and its ad-serving service provider, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information.

Our Cookies are mainly maintained to track our affiliates and/or other sales partners to ensure proper payments for their sales and tracking activities relating to their affiliate relationship with us.

**Links**

We may offer links from our website and software to other third party websites which may be hosted by our co-branding partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites are not governed by this privacy policy and ShieldApps makes no representation as to their practices for dealing with your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit.

**Security**

The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain such safeguards to protect security of servers and your personally identifiable information.

We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, provide customer service, or maintain your account with us.

**Policy Modifications**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you in order to reflect our practices and provide greater protection for your information. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted promptly here, so please check back periodically.

**Acceptance of Terms**

By using the ShieldApps services, accessing the ShieldApps products and/or company website and/or software sites you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection and use that are described in this Privacy Policy.
